<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>933.1331-2</version>
		<change>Fixed iOS 12.4.1 and below back button issue.</change>
        <change>Added the ability to import json files in Import Friends List.</change>
        <change>Added Start Over, day 0.</change>
        <change>Enabled Auto Dark Mode setting for Notched devices. Intended for users who enable auto dark/light or set dark light in ios Settings. (Notched devices status bar was remaining dark with dark status.)</change>
        <change>Reset Preferences file, incorrect group/user.</change>
        <change>Known issues: CSources2 Re-spring broken, use Power App etc. instead.</change>
	</changes>
    <changes>
        <version>933.1331-0</version>
        <change>iOS 9.3.3-13.3.1 unc0ver / checkra1n supported. Currently as long as the jailbreak is using sources.list.d folder for its sources.</change>
        <change>Added Multi Delete.UI</change>
        <change>Updated the Apply, now remembers.</change>
        <change>GUI inprovments.</change>
        <change>Added Packages Refresh Counts Reminder feature. Look at How To or Read blog for full details.</change>
        <change>Updated Activity indicators.</change>
        <change>StatusBar correction for dark mode.Added Dark/Light Mode Theme. Not yet complete.</change>
        <change>Added Cydia Tweaks Page.</change>
        <change>Icon Retrieval Update now leaves existing icon until a new one is found.</change>
        <change>And of course some 🐞🐜🐛🕷🦟 's</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
        <version>600.1323-0</version>
        <change>iOS 6.0.0-13.2.3 Support, Utilizing checkra1n exploit. Possible unc0ver.</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
        <version>600.1302-1</version>
        <change><![CDATA[
            UI Modifications.<br/>
        iOS 6.0.0-13.x.x Support, posibile 13.2.3 & 13.3.<br/>
        iPad7,5 - 7,6 - 7,11 - 7,12 - 11,3 - 11,4 - 8,7 - 8,8 - 11,1 - 11,2 Support.<br/>
        iPhone12,1 - 12,3 - 12,5 Support.<br/>
        CSources2 now shows repos that are already loaded into Cydia. If source is in Cydia, the source will be disabled in CSources2 and will have an orange tint.
        Improved MultiSync.<br/>
        Added Mark As IsSafe/UnSafe.<br/>
        Added option to reset all settings via Settings. Also added option via the +(add new source) , type resetcs2defaults as if you were adding a new source.<br/>
        Please note, when attempting to open a terminal app via CSources2, if the developer of the installed terminal app does not have a URLScheme for its app, then CSources2 cannot open it.<br/>
        Webview improvements.<br/>
        Fixed SlideOver/Splitview.<br/>
        AutoSave improvements<br/>
        New Settings.<br/>
        Fixed open in app / safari.<br/>
        XS Max, 11, 11Pro, 11ProMax etc compatibility.<br/>
        Fixes for User Icons.<br/>
        Improved icon download timing.<br/>
        Auto Scrolling to new sources etc, improvements.<br/>
        Browser now has static history(beta). By default, CS2 does not remember sites in Browser, turn on Static History, this can be flushed in settings.<br/>
        User can mark a source as Safe (IsSafe) or UnSafe.<br/>
        Currently fully tested on unc0ver (Undecimus-v3.7.0.b3), Cydia64_1.1.32~b22.<br/>
        Backgrounding has been improved to allow coming back and forth or sidebyside integration.<br/>
        App Colors features / color theming improvements.<br/>
        And much more.....<br/>
        ]]></change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
        <version>600.1121-1</version>
        <change>bug fix, if toggling repo on/off while searching &on or &off, search would crash.</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
        <version>600.812-3</version>
        <change>Re-written from scratch. New look, New everything.</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
        <version>600.812-0</version>
        <change>Second Initial Release</change>
    </changes>
</changelog>
